Tufts University School of Medicine Yearbook UP150
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- School of Medicine Yearbook, 1924 -- 2020; UP150.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 80 Volumes; 5757 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987 [yearbook], UP150.001.046.00001 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 47, UP150.001.046.00001.00050 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 48, UP150.001.046.00001.00051 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 49, UP150.001.046.00001.00052 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 50, UP150.001.046.00001.00053 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 51, UP150.001.046.00001.00054 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 52, UP150.001.046.00001.00055 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 53, UP150.001.046.00001.00056 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 54, UP150.001.046.00001.00057 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 55, UP150.001.046.00001.00058 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 56, UP150.001.046.00001.00059 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 57, UP150.001.046.00001.00060 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 58, UP150.001.046.00001.00061 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 59, UP150.001.046.00001.00062 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 60, UP150.001.046.00001.00063 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 61, UP150.001.046.00001.00064 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 62, UP150.001.046.00001.00065 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 63, UP150.001.046.00001.00066 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 64, UP150.001.046.00001.00067 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 65, UP150.001.046.00001.00068 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 66, UP150.001.046.00001.00069 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 67, UP150.001.046.00001.00070 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 68, UP150.001.046.00001.00071 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 69, UP150.001.046.00001.00072 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 70, UP150.001.046.00001.00073 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 71, UP150.001.046.00001.00074 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 72, UP150.001.046.00001.00075 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 73, UP150.001.046.00001.00076 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 74, UP150.001.046.00001.00077 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 75, UP150.001.046.00001.00078 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 76, UP150.001.046.00001.00079 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 77, UP150.001.046.00001.00080 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 78, UP150.001.046.00001.00081 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 79, UP150.001.046.00001.00082 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 80, UP150.001.046.00001.00083 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 81, UP150.001.046.00001.00084 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 82, UP150.001.046.00001.00085 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 83, UP150.001.046.00001.00086 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 84, UP150.001.046.00001.00087 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 85, UP150.001.046.00001.00088 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 86, UP150.001.046.00001.00089 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 87, UP150.001.046.00001.00090 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 88, UP150.001.046.00001.00091 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 89, UP150.001.046.00001.00092 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 90, UP150.001.046.00001.00093 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 91, UP150.001.046.00001.00094 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 92, UP150.001.046.00001.00095 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 93, UP150.001.046.00001.00096 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 94, UP150.001.046.00001.00097 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 95, UP150.001.046.00001.00098 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 96, UP150.001.046.00001.00099 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 97, UP150.001.046.00001.00100 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 98, UP150.001.046.00001.00101 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 99, UP150.001.046.00001.00102 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 100, UP150.001.046.00001.00103 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 101, UP150.001.046.00001.00104 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 102, UP150.001.046.00001.00105 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 103, UP150.001.046.00001.00106 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 104, UP150.001.046.00001.00107 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 105, UP150.001.046.00001.00108 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 106, UP150.001.046.00001.00109 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 107, UP150.001.046.00001.00110 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 108, UP150.001.046.00001.00111 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 109, UP150.001.046.00001.00112 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 110, UP150.001.046.00001.00113 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 111, UP150.001.046.00001.00114 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 112, UP150.001.046.00001.00115 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 113, UP150.001.046.00001.00116 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 114, UP150.001.046.00001.00117 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 115, UP150.001.046.00001.00118 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 116, UP150.001.046.00001.00119 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 117, UP150.001.046.00001.00120 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 118, UP150.001.046.00001.00121 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 119, UP150.001.046.00001.00122 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 120, UP150.001.046.00001.00123 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 121, UP150.001.046.00001.00124 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 122, UP150.001.046.00001.00125 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 123, UP150.001.046.00001.00126 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 124, UP150.001.046.00001.00127 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 125, UP150.001.046.00001.00128 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 126, UP150.001.046.00001.00129 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 127, UP150.001.046.00001.00130 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 128, UP150.001.046.00001.00131 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 129, UP150.001.046.00001.00132 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 130, UP150.001.046.00001.00133 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 131, UP150.001.046.00001.00134 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 132, UP150.001.046.00001.00135 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 133, UP150.001.046.00001.00136 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 134, UP150.001.046.00001.00137 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 135, UP150.001.046.00001.00138 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 136, UP150.001.046.00001.00139 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 137, UP150.001.046.00001.00140 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 138, UP150.001.046.00001.00141 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 139, UP150.001.046.00001.00142 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 140, UP150.001.046.00001.00143 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 141, UP150.001.046.00001.00144 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 142, UP150.001.046.00001.00145 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 143, UP150.001.046.00001.00146 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 144, UP150.001.046.00001.00147 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 145, UP150.001.046.00001.00148 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 146, UP150.001.046.00001.00149 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 147, UP150.001.046.00001.00150 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 148, UP150.001.046.00001.00151 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 149, UP150.001.046.00001.00152 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 150, UP150.001.046.00001.00153 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 151, UP150.001.046.00001.00154 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 152, UP150.001.046.00001.00155 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 153, UP150.001.046.00001.00156 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 154, UP150.001.046.00001.00157 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 155, UP150.001.046.00001.00158 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 156, UP150.001.046.00001.00159 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 157, UP150.001.046.00001.00160 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 158, UP150.001.046.00001.00161 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 159, UP150.001.046.00001.00162 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, page 160, UP150.001.046.00001.00163 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, inside back cover, left, UP150.001.046.00001.00164 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, inside back cover, right, UP150.001.046.00001.00165 (Volume 46)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine 1987, back cover, UP150.001.046.00001.00166 (Volume 46)
  - Medical Yearbook, 1988; UP150.001.047 (Volume 47)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine Medical Record [yearbook], 1989; UP150.001.060.00001 (Volume 60)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1989.
    - Medical Record, front cover, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00001 (Volume 60)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1989
    - Medical Record, page 1, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00002 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 2, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00003 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 3, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00004 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 4, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00005 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 5, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00006 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 6, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00007 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 7, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00008 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 8, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00009 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 9, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00010 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 10, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00011 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 11, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00012 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 12, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00013 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 13, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00014 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 14, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00015 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 15, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00016 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 16, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00017 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 17, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00018 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 18, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00019 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 19, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00020 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 20, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00021 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 21, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00022 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 22, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00023 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 23, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00024 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 24, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00025 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 25, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00026 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 26, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00027 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 27, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00028 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 28, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00029 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 29, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00030 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 30, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00031 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 31, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00032 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 32, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00033 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 33, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00034 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 34, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00035 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 35, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00036 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 36, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00037 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 37, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00038 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 38, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00039 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 39, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00040 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 40, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00041 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 41, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00042 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 42, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00043 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 43, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00044 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 44, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00045 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 45, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00046 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 46, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00047 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 47, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00048 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 48, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00049 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 49, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00050 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 50, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00051 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 51, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00052 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 52, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00053 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 53, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00054 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 54, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00055 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 55, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00056 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 56, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00057 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 57, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00058 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 58, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00059 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 59, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00060 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 60, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00061 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 61, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00062 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 62, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00063 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 63, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00064 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 64, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00065 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 65, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00066 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 66, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00067 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 67, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00068 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 68, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00069 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 69, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00070 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 70, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00071 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 71, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00072 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 72, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00073 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 73, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00074 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 74, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00075 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 75, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00076 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 76, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00077 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 77, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00078 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 78, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00079 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 79, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00080 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 80, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00081 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 81, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00082 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 82, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00083 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 83, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00084 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 84, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00085 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 85, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00086 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 86, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00087 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 87, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00088 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 88, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00089 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 89, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00090 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 90, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00091 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 91, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00092 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 92, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00093 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 93, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00094 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 94, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00095 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 95, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00096 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 96, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00097 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 97, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00098 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 98, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00099 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 99, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00100 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 100, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00101 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 101, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00102 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 102, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00103 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 103, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00104 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 104, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00105 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 105, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00106 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 106, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00107 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 107, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00108 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 108, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00109 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 109, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00110 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 110, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00111 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 111, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00112 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 112, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00113 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 113, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00114 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 114, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00115 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 115, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00116 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 116, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00117 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 117, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00118 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 118, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00119 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 119, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00120 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 120, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00121 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 121, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00122 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 122, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00123 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 123, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00124 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 124, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00125 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 125, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00126 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 126, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00127 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 127, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00128 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 128, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00129 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 129, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00130 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 130, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00131 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 131, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00132 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 132, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00133 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 133, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00134 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 134, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00135 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 135, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00136 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 136, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00137 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 137, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00138 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 138, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00139 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 139, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00140 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 140, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00141 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 141, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00142 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 142, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00143 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 143, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00144 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 144, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00145 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 145, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00146 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 146, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00147 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 147, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00148 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 148, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00149 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 149, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00150 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 150, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00151 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 151, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00152 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 152, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00153 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 153, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00154 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 154, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00155 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 155, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00156 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 156, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00157 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 157, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00158 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 158, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00159 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 159, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00160 (Volume 60)
    - Medical Record, page 160, 1989; UP150.001.060.00001.00161 (Volume 60)